Berliner Gramophone Disc Collection
Yale University Music Library
- Recordings, Series I
  - Madchen's Wunsch v. Chopin; Kath Senger-Bettaque; 43071, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009002)
    Disc No. 43071
  - Es hat die Rose sich beklagt; Kath Senger-Bettaque; 43070, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009010)
    Disc No. 43070
  - Ueberden Bergen wohnt das Gluck; Kath Senger-Bettaque; 43069, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009028)
    Disc No. 43068
  - Derverliabte Bua v. Millocker; Hermine Mayerhofer; 43065, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009036)
    Disc No. 43065
  - Goldfischlied a. Geisha; Annie Birkens; 43053, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009044)
    Disc No. 43053
  - Arie a. Lucia di Lammermoor; Sophie Heymann; 43050, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009051)
    Disc No. 43050
  - Arie a. Lucia di Lammermoor; Sophie Heymann; 43050, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009069)
  - Der Vogel im Walde v. Taubert; Sophie Heymann; 43048, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009077)
    Disc No. 43048
  - Schwebisches Volkslieb; Paula Worm; 43016, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009085)
    Disc No. 43016
  - Styrienne aus Mignon; Selma Kurz; 43014, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009093)
    Disc No. 43014
  - Der Erangelinand; Edith Walley; 43000, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009101)
    Disc No. 43000
  - Pastorale aus Prophet; K. K. Kammersanger Hermann Winkelmann; 2-42332, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009119)
    Disc No. 2-42332
  - Marcell's Segen aus, Hugenotten; Wilhelm Hesch, K. K. Kammersanger Hermann; 2-42351, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009127)
    Disc No. 2-42351
  - Keine Ruh' bei Tag und Nacht a. Don Juan; Wilhelm Hesch, K. K. Kammersanger; 2-42316, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009135)
    Disc No. 2-42316
  - Im tiefen Keller; Rich. Mayr, K. K. Hofopernsanger; 2-42309, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009143)
    Disc No. 2-42309
  - Is das ein schoner Mann; Richard Waldemak; 2-42291, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009150)
    Disc No. 2-42291
  - Gebet aus Lohengrin; Richard Mayr, K.K Hofopernsanger; 2-42286, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009168)
    Disc No. 2-42286
  - Pfeiflied aus Fruhlingsluft; Johannes Semfke; 2-42149, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009176)
    Disc No. 2-42149
  - Zufriedenheit, aus der Puppe; Alexander Haydter; 2-42139, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009184)
    Disc No. 2-42139
  - Stretta aus Troubadour; Leo Slezak, K.K Hofopernsanger; 2-42126, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009192)
    Disc No. 2-42126
  - Sittencommissions-Couplet; Alexander Girardi Wien; 2-42122, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009200)
    Disc No. 2-42122
  - Grosser Gott hor mein Fleh'n; K.K Hofopernsanger Leo Slezak; 2-42095, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009218)
    Disc No. 2-42095
  - Standchen aus Troubadour; Leo Slezak, K.K Hofopernsanger; 2-42092, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009226)
    Disc No. 2-42092
  - Mein Schatz ist im Keller die Tonne; Carl Nebe; 2-42046, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009234)
    Disc No. 2-42046
  - Cadenz des Beppo; Julius Lieban, kgl. Hofopernsanger; 2-42035, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009242)
    Disc No. 2-42035
  - Ich wollt, ich war' ein Schmetterling; Fritz Schrodter; 2-42025, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009259)
    Disc No. 2-42025
  - Hell schmetternd ruft die Lerche; Leep. Demuth, k. u. k. Hofopernsanger; 2-42021, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009267)
    Disc No. 2-42021
  - Gralserzahlung aus Lohengrin; Erik Schmedes, k. u. k Kammersanger; 2-42008, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009275)
    Disc No. 2-42008
  - Was bin ich aufgewacht; Franz Naval, k. u. k Kammersanger; 2-42007, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009283)
    Disc No. 2-42007
  - Kommt er dann heim; Franz Naval, k. u. k Kammersanger; 2-42000, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009291)
    Disc No. 2-42000
  - Tempelscene des Salomo; Leop Demuth, k. u. k Hofopernsanger; 42730, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009309)
    Disc No. 42780
  - Lockruf; Leop Demuth, k. u. k Hofopernsanger; 42779, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009317)
    Disc No. 42779
  - Bruderlein und Schwesterlein; Fritz Schrodter, k. u. k Kammersanger; 42776, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009325)
    Disc No. 42776
  - Am Spmnra; Leop Demuth, k. u. k Hofopernsanger; 42770, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009333)
    Disc No. 42770
  - Besenbinderlied aus Bansel und Gretel; Benedikt Felix, k. u. k Hofopernsanger; 42766, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009341)
  - Zigeunermelodie; Wilhelm Hesch, k. u. k Kammersanger; 42764, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009358)
    Disc No. 42764
  - Ich hatte nicht daran gedacht; K. u. k Hofopernsangerin Frances Saville; 43185, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009366)
    Disc No. 43185
  - Mir traumte von einem Konigskind; Laura Hilgermann; 43186, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009374)
    Disc No. 43186
  - Auf dem Meere, von Robert Franz; K. u. k. Hofopernsangerin Edith Walker; 43190, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009382)
    Disc No. 43190
  - Eruhlingsnacht, von Schumann; K. u. K. Hofopernsangerin Edith Walker; 43191, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009390)
    Disc No. 43191
  - Heidenroslein; Minnie Nast; 43193, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009408)
  - Wiegnlied [unintelligble]; Laura Hilgermann; 43196, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009416)
    Disc No. 43196
  - Coppelia-Walzer; Ellen Brandt-Forster; 43198, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009424)
    Disc No. 43198
  - Heidenroslein; Frances Saville; 43300, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009432)
    Disc No. 43300
  - Der Vogel im Walde; Selma Kurz, k.u.k. Hofopernsangerin; 43302, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009440)
    Disc No. 43302
  - Sommerabend; Margarethe Michalek; 43303, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009457)
    Disc No. 43303
  - Arie der Konigin; Edith Walker; 43304, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009465)
    Disc No. 43304
  - Arie der Konigin; Edith Walker; 43304, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009473)
  - Canzone des Pagen; Selma Kurz; 43305, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009481)
    Disc No. 43305
  - Susserdie Glockennieklingen; Anni Bremer; 43311, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009499)
    Disc No. 43311
  - Wie Stolz und stattlich geht er; Marie Knuepfer-Egli; 43314, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009507)
    Disc No. 43314
  - Mein Liebster ist ein Weber; Laura Hilgermann; 43317, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009515)
    Disc No. 43317
  - Schusterlied v. Weingartner; Marie Gutheil-Schoder, Hofoper; 43320, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009523)
    Disc No. 43320
  - Fredy-Walzer; Josefine Kraus; 43326, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009531)
    Disc No. 43326
  - D MInbauerin; Dora Keplinger; 43333, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009549)
    Disc No. 43333
  - Wiegenlied; Marie Gotze, kgl. Kammersangerin; 43357, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009556)
    Disc No. 43357
  - Recitativ und Arie aus Fidelio; Lucie Weidt, k.k. Hofopernsangerin; 43380, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009564)
    Disc No. 43380
  - Ariette aus Lakme; Grete Forst, K.K. Hofopernsangerin; 43382, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009572)
    Disc No. 43382
  - Lied der Lola aus Cavalleria rusticana; Beatrix Kernic; 43392, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009580)
    Disc No. 43392
  - Scene des Taumannchen aus Hansel und Gretel ;Marie knupfer-Egli, kgl. Hofopernsangerin; 43399, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009598)
    Disc No. 43399
  - Es giebt ein Gluck a Lohengrin; Pelagie Greef-Andriessen u. Elsa Schweizer; 44018, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009606)
    Disc No. 44018
  - Der lustige Ehemann; Gertrud Runge u. Robert Leonhardt; 44030, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009614)
    Disc No. 44030
  - So lang hab ich geschmachtet; Ellen Drandt Forster und Loop. Demuth; 44115, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009622)
    Disc No. 44115
  - Der lustige Ehemann; Gertrud Runge und Paul Steinegg; 44355, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009630)
    Disc No. 44355
  - Tantum ergo; Stephanschor; 44532, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009648)
    Disc No. 44532
  - Ave Maria; Stephanschor; 44533, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009655)
    Disc No. 44533
  - Zigeunerweisen; Concertmeister Rose; 47917, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009663)
    Disc No. 47917
  - Il cantastorie; Fercor; 51149, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009671)
    Disc No. 51149
  - Panis Angelicus; Perruccio Corradetti; 52204, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009689)
    Disc No. 52204
  - Barbiere di Siviglia; Luigi Montecucchi; 52233, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125667742)
    Disc No. 52233
  - Maria di Rohan; Ferruccio Corradetti; 52242, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009697)
    Disc No. 52242
  - Romanza di Dennza; Ferruccio Corradetti; 52243, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009705)
    Disc No. 52243
  - Pagliacci; Giuseppe Oxilia; 52246, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009713)
    Disc No. 52246
  - Senzatetto senza cuna; Ferruccio Corradetti; 52247, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009721)
    Disc No. 52247
  - I Due Foscari; Ferruccio Corradetti; 52264, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009739)
    Disc No. 52264
  - Tosca; Carlo Caffetto; 52266, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009747)
    Disc No. 52266
  - Norma; Carlo Caffetto; 52268, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009754)
    Disc No. 52268
  - Norma; Carlo Caffetto; 52269, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009762)
    Disc No. 52269
  - Che Buo Fa; Francesco Daddi; 52273, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009770)
    Disc No. 52273
  - Traviata; Giuseppe Oxelia; 52274, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009788)
    Disc No. 52274
  - Traviata; Giuseppe Oxilia; 52275, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009796)
    Disc No. 52275
  - Manon (Puccini); Giovanni Apostulo; 52284, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009804)
    Disc No. 52284
  - LUcia di Lammermoor; [unintelligible]; 52286, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009812)
    Disc No. 52286
  - Lucrezia Borgia; Ignazio Oddo; 52287, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009820)
    Disc No. 52287
  - Ernani; Ignazio Oddo; 52290, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009838)
    Disc No. 52290
  - Merce dilelli amico; Carlo Caffetto; 52462, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009846)
    Disc No. 52462
  - [unintelligible]; Carlo Caffette; 52463, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009853)
    Disc No. 52463
  - Esultate Otello Verdi; Carlo Caffetto; 52484, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009861)
    Disc No. 52484
  - Esultate Otello; Carlo Caffetto; 52434, undated; 1 (Box 737, Item barcode 39002125009879)
    Disc No. 52434
  - Di Quella Pira; Carlo Caffetto; 52494, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125009903)
    Disc No. 52494
  - Sisciliana Car. Rui. Mascagni; Carlo Caffetto; 52495X, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125009911)
    Disc No. 52495X
  - O Paradiso Africana; Carlo Caffetto; 52541, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125009929)
    Disc No. 52541
  - Toreador Carmen; Canlala dal Sio Moreo; 52544, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125009937)
    Disc No. 52544
  - Codligiani vid nazza dammata; Canlala dal Sio Moreo; 52553, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125009945)
    Disc No. 52553
  - Di Provenza il man il sual; Canlala dal Sio Moreo; 52555, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125667759)
    Disc No. 52555
  - Il Lalen del sua sorriso; Canlala dal Sio Moreo; 52544, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125009952)
    Disc No. 52546
  - Vesti La guibba [unintelligible]; Canlala dal Sio Caffetto; 52558, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125009960)
    Disc No. 52558
  - Carzone del Joreodor; Canlala dal Signor Moreo; 52561, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125009978)
    Disc No. 52561
  - Santa Medaglia; Canlala dal Signor Moreo; 52562, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125667767)
    Disc No. 52562
  - Veechia Gimarra; Canlala dal Cavative Nicoletti; 52564, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125009986)
    Disc No. 52564
  - H fior che avevi a me tu dato; Canlala dal Sig Cisasani; 52565, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125009994)
    Disc No. 52565
  - Spinto genlili; Canlala dal Signor Cisasani; 52568, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125010000)
    Disc No. 52568
  - Inofelica e tin credear; Cantata dal Eavaline Nicoletta; 52569, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520015)
    Disc No. 52569
  - Duetto dir buganti; Cantata dal Signor Coradetti; 52572, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520023)
    Disc No. 52572
  - Largo al Factotuin; Cantata dal Signor Coradetti; 52576, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520031)
    Disc No. 52576
  - Inainoi belle bruine [unintelligible]; Cantata dal Signor Cesarain; 52585, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520049)
    Disc No. 52585
  - Il Dio dell'or; Cantata dal Sig Fianeli; 52592, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520056)
    Disc No. 52592
  - Demon failar al misero; Cantata dal Sig Moreo; 52613, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125667775)
    Disc No. 52613
  - Je Gran Dottore; Cantata dal Sig Fantone; 52614, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520064)
    Disc No. 52614
  - Di Linesta Pinar; Cantata dal Sig Cesarani; 52615, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520072)
    Disc No. 52615
  - Norma; Jgnazio Odio; 52810, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520080)
    Disc No. 52810
  - Barbiere Di Siviglia; Ferruccio Corradetti; 52833, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520098)
    Disc No. 52833
  - Serenata di Brighella; Emilio Riguzzi; 52812, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520106)
    Disc No. 52812
  - Giulia; Emilio Bucalo; 52815, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520114)
    Disc No. 52815
  - Boheme; Lorenzo Capponi; 52820, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520122)
    Disc No. 52820
  - Guarany; Guiseppe Ia Puma; 52830, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520130)
    Disc No. 52830
  - Fra Diavolo; Ferruccio Corradetti; 52834, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520148)
    Disc No. 52834
  - Rigoletto; Emilio Uucalo; 52648, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520155)
    Disc No. 52848
  - Donna Vorrei Morir; Giuseppe Giusti; 52853, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520163)
    Disc No. 52853
  - Sogno (Tosti); Giuseppe Giusti; 52856, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520171)
    Disc No. 52856
  - Carmen (Bizet); Orchesta; 50700, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520189)
    Disc No. 50700
  - Siberia (Giordano); Gino Martinez Patti; 52884, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520197)
    Disc No. 52884
  - Poliuto (Donizzetti); Luigi Colazza; 52890, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520205)
    Disc No. 52890
  - Il Trovatore (Verdi); Giovanni Valis; 52897, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520213)
    Disc No. 52897
  - Cavalleria Rusticana; Bice Adami; 53110, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125667783)
    Disc No. 53110
  - Trovatore; Rita Casini; 53122, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125667791)
    Disc No. 53122
  - Boheme (Puccini); Bice Adami; 53117, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520221)
    Disc No. 53117
  - Manon (Massenet); Bice Adami; 53118X, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520239)
    Disc No. 53118X
  - Forza Del Destino; Ernestina Tebro e Coro; 53130, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520247)
    Disc No. 53130
  - Trovatore; Elisa Bruno; 53132, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520254)
    Disc No. 53132
  - Linda di Chamounix; Elisa Bruno; 53133, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520262)
    Disc No. 53133
  - Gioconda, Suicidio; Ernestina Tebro; 53134, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520270)
    Disc No. 53134
  - I vespri Siciliani (Verdi); La Senorita Josefina Huguet; 53138, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520288)
    Disc No. 53138
  - Traviata (Verdi); La Senorita Josefina Huguet; 53139, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520296)
    Disc No. 53139
  - Linda Di Chamounix (Donizetti); La Senorita Josefina Huguet; 53141, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520304)
    Disc No. 53141
  - Manon (Puccini); Cesira Ferrani; 53147, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520312)
    Disc No. 53147
  - Desiderio - Romanza; Cesira Ferrani; 53148, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125667809)
    Disc No. 53148
  - Erodiade; Cesira Ferrani; 53149, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125667817)
    Disc No. 53149
  - Lohengrin; Cesira Ferrani; 53150, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125667825)
    Disc No. 53150
  - Un Ballo in Maschera (Verdi); Emma Trentini; 53153, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520320)
    Disc No. 53153
  - Un Ballo in Maschera (Verdi); Emma Trentini; 53155, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002126520338)
    Disc No. 53155
  - Erhani Chvolami (Verdi); [unintelligible]; 53158, undated; 1 (Box 738, Item barcode 39002125667833)
    Disc No. 53158
  - Du gamla du friska...; Operasangaren Karl Lundquist; 82643, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520346)
    Disc No. 82643
  - Romans ur Operan Mefistofeles; Henning Malm, Operasangaren; 82530, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520353)
    Disc No. 82530
  - Vallarelat af J. Wideen; Operasangaren John Forsell; 82500, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520361)
    Disc No. 82500
  - a. Laulaja poika, b. Lintuselle; sjungen af Operasangaren A. Ojanpera ackompagnerad af O. Merikanto; 82086, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520379)
    Disc No. 82086
  - Marcella Lindt; [unintelligible]; 73161, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520387)
    Disc No. 73161
  - Narodini pisep Allgaiko me dite; Ruz Maturove; 73026, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520395)
    Disc No. 73026
  - Tot Leanybol: Lczi, Piczi Nyul...; Blaha Lujza; 73016, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520403)
    Disc No. 73016
  - Kukoricza Janes belepoje; Pinter lmre a budapesti nepszinhaz tagja; 72768, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520411)
    Disc No. 72768
  - Kdyz Zdenek muj z op. Daliber (Sinetana); Ottokar Marek; 72754, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520429)
    Disc No. 72754
  - Pred durmi of der Thure; Franz Naval; 72646, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520437)
    Disc No. 72646
  - Fialky (Vayta Kuchynka); Franz Pacal, K.K. Hofopernsanger; 72639, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520445)
    Disc No. 72639
  - Kdezly Te Marenko nemiloval [unintelligible]; Franz Pacal, K.K. Hofopernsanger; 72638, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520452)
    Disc No. 72638
  - Za jedan casat; [unintelligible]; 72636, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520460)
    Disc No. 72636
  - [unintelligible]; 72591, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520478)
    Disc No. 72591
  - Abendstern; Maxillanousk; 72587, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520486)
    Disc No. 72587
  - Die Lotosbluine; Max Ulanowski; 72585, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520494)
    Disc No. 72585
  - Rude ruze; Franz Pacl, K.K. Hofopernsanger; 72463, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520502)
    Disc No. 72463
  - Gdje Standk moj2; Albian Lukaseh; Agram; Tenor; 72462, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520510)
    Disc No. 72462
  - Fjariln vingad syns pa haga; Operettsangaren G. A. Lund; 72195, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520528)
    Disc No. 72195
  - El Bateo (Chucca); Sr. Alba y Sa. Gurina; 64024, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520536)
    Disc No. 64024
  - La Tempranica (Gimenez) la Senorita Marina Gurina (Tiple) (Extra Disc), undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520544)
    Disc No. 63360
  - Spanish Soprano; La Tempranica; La Senorita Marina Gurina, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520551)
    Disc No. 63351
  - Spanish Soprano; Nina Pancha; Romea y Valverde; La Senorita Josefina Huguet, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520569)
    Disc No. 63240
  - La Garina; Senora Martinez; 63167, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520577)
    Disc No. 63167
  - El Rey que rabio; Cantado for Senora Martinez; 63177, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520585)
    Disc No. 63177
  - Sevillanas No. 1; Cantadas por el Sr. Antonio Pozo; 62805, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520593)
    Disc No. 62805
  - Guernikako Arbola; Snr. Moreno (Baritono); 62863, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520601)
    Disc No. 62863
  - La Bruja; Snr. Bezares; 62860, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520619)
    Disc No. 62860
  - Guaji Cuba; el. Mochuelo; 62781, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520627)
    Disc No. 62781
  - Mujer Y Reina (Chapi); el Senor Marino Aineto (Baritono); 62696, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520635)
    Disc No. 62696
  - Sueno de La Casa de Dios; Sr. Pinedo; 61125, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520643)
    Disc No. 61125
  - Milonga; El Sr. Don Inrique Gil; 61112, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520650)
    Disc No. 61112
  - La Alegria de la Huerta; el Sr. Don Inrique Gil; 61111, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520668)
    Disc No. 61111
  - [unintelligible]; Prof. Moreschi; 54758, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520676)
    Disc No. 54758
  - La lua Santuzza; Cantata dal Sig Cesarana; 54116, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520684)
    Disc No. 54116
  - Miserere; Cantata dalla Sig Cesarana; 54113, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002125667841)
    Disc No. 54113
  - Fiar vuro lasciarte; Cantata dal Sig Cesarana; 54110, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520692)
    Disc No. 54110
  - Pur ti riveggo mua dolce auda; Cantata dal Sig Cesarana; 54108, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520700)
    Disc No. 54108
  - Una Snora mir lasciaste; Cantata dal Sig Cesarana; 54102, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520718)
    Disc No. 54102
  - Betu m amu; Cantata dal Sig Moreo; 54098, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520726)
    Disc No. 54098
  - Mira d'acerbe laguine; Cantata dal Sig Coriadetti e dalla; 54097, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520734)
    Disc No. 54097
  - Dite alla giovanel; Cantata dal Sig Corradelle e dalla; 54101, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520742)
    Disc No. 54101
  - Lardi Sijarliddio Faust-Gounod; Sig Snippa Big Cattetto; 54084, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002125667858)
    Disc No. 54084
  - Fra Diavolo; Duetto dei briganti; 54070, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002125667866)
    Disc No. 54070
  - O Rre Nuosto; Signorina Andreace; 53193, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520759)
    Disc No. 53193
  - Le Fraslate d'amor; Cantata dalla Sig Galan; 53190, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002125667874)
    Disc No. 53190
  - Una voce foco ja; Cantata dal Sig Galon; 53184, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002125667882)
    Disc No. 53184
  - Jo sou la farfalla; Cantata dal Sig adaum; 53178, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002126520767)
    Disc No. 53178
  - Che Faro seiza [unintelligible]; Cantata dal Sig Galare; 54758, undated; 1 (Box 739, Item barcode 39002125667890)